<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Sciences</title>
    <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Data Sciences</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 07:36:10 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://unodatasciences.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/projects/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 07:36:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/projects/projects/</guid>
      <description> About our Work Research at the Consulting Lab explores novel uses for large-scale heterogeneous data to understand the behavior of individuals, firms, societies and economies.
Featured Projects     OLLAS OLLAS--   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Direction Map</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/direction-map/direction_map/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 07:36:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/direction-map/direction_map/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this is Direction Map page. Data Science is the art and science of transforming raw data into deliverable data products in order to help businesses or government agencies make more informed decisions. The Concentration in Data Science consists of eight major components: Data Visualization, Scientific Methods, Statistical Modeling, Statistical Computing, Real-world Data Applications, Data Consulting, Data Research, and Data Technology.
The Concentration in Data Science prepares students for a job as a Data Scientist, as well as providing a strong background for many other careers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/services/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 07:27:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/services/services/</guid>
      <description>This is Services page. Data Science is the art and science of transforming raw data into deliverable data products in order to help businesses or government agencies make more informed decisions. The Concentration in Data Science consists of eight major components: Data Visualization, Scientific Methods, Statistical Modeling, Statistical Computing, Real-world Data Applications, Data Consulting, Data Research, and Data Technology.
The Concentration in Data Science prepares students for a job as a Data Scientist, as well as providing a strong background for many other careers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/people/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 07:22:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/people/people/</guid>
      <description>       Xiaoyue Cheng , PhD
Assistant Professor
DSC 225 / 402.554.2848
Email: xycheng@unomaha.edu
 Betty N. Love, PhD
Associate Professor
DSC 224 / 402.554.2831
Email: blove@unomaha.edu
 Mahbubul Majumder, PhD
Assistant Professor
DSC 238 / 402.554.2734
Email: mmajumder@unomaha.edu
 Andrew W. Swift, DSc
Associate Professor
DSC 237 / 402.554.3637
Email: aswift@unomaha.edu   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting Lab</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 07:03:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/about/about/</guid>
      <description>About Us Consulting Lab is committed to providing UNO faculty, staff, and students with free consultation on research and survey design, data collection and management, statistical analysis, and evaluation. Consultants have extensive training in applied statistics and research methods, and can offer advice for both quantitative and qualitative research. The Consulting Lab also strives to provide appropriate introductory training with common data analysis software.
Consulting Services Consulting services include advice and training:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operations Research</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/operations-research/operations_research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/operations-research/operations_research/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The department has several researchers in statistics and operations research. We plan to develop research problems in data science in collaboration with the local community. This will strengthen the academic research program and lay the foundation for a possible future doctorate in Data Science.
Concentrations in Data Science The Department of Mathematics offers a concentration in Data Science for undergraduate students pursuing a BA or BS degree, as well as for graduate students pursuing a MS degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/statistics/statics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/statistics/statics/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Statistics program offers courses emphasizing the practical aspect of probability and statistics. The program serves the needs of future statisticians in science, industry, business, and government. In addition, it provides the necessary background and stimulation for graduate study. It is also a crucial component of Actuarial Sciences.
Concentrations in Data Science The Department of Mathematics offers a concentration in Data Science for undergraduate students pursuing a BA or BS degree, as well as for graduate students pursuing a MS degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data science</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/data-scicence/data_science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/data-scicence/data_science/</guid>
      <description>What is Data Science? Data Science is the art and science of transforming raw data into deliverable data products in order to help businesses or government agencies make more informed decisions. The Concentration in Data Science consists of eight major components: Data Visualization, Scientific Methods, Statistical Modeling, Statistical Computing, Real-world Data Applications, Data Consulting, Data Research, and Data Technology.
The Concentration in Data Science prepares students for a job as a Data Scientist, as well as providing a strong background for many other careers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office of Latino/Latin American Studies</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/projects/ollas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/projects/ollas/</guid>
      <description>img {float:left;}   The Office of Latino/Latin American Studies (OLLAS) was created to ensure that UNO students and the community have the education and the skills needed to understand the connection of Latinos, Latin America and some of the most important issues of our times. Understanding the multiple root causes and socio-economic, political and cultural impacts of these populations has become a critical component of a true liberal arts education and is central to the development of an informed and engaged citizenry.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>