<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science on Data Sciences</title>
    <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/tags/data-science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science on Data Sciences</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:52 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://unodatasciences.github.io/tags/data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Operations Research</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/operations-research/operations_research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/operations-research/operations_research/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The department has several researchers in statistics and operations research. We plan to develop research problems in data science in collaboration with the local community. This will strengthen the academic research program and lay the foundation for a possible future doctorate in Data Science.
Concentrations in Data Science The Department of Mathematics offers a concentration in Data Science for undergraduate students pursuing a BA or BS degree, as well as for graduate students pursuing a MS degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/statistics/statics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/statistics/statics/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Statistics program offers courses emphasizing the practical aspect of probability and statistics. The program serves the needs of future statisticians in science, industry, business, and government. In addition, it provides the necessary background and stimulation for graduate study. It is also a crucial component of Actuarial Sciences.
Concentrations in Data Science The Department of Mathematics offers a concentration in Data Science for undergraduate students pursuing a BA or BS degree, as well as for graduate students pursuing a MS degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data science</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/data-scicence/data_science/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/data-scicence/data_science/</guid>
      <description>What is Data Science? Data Science is the art and science of transforming raw data into deliverable data products in order to help businesses or government agencies make more informed decisions. The Concentration in Data Science consists of eight major components: Data Visualization, Scientific Methods, Statistical Modeling, Statistical Computing, Real-world Data Applications, Data Consulting, Data Research, and Data Technology.
The Concentration in Data Science prepares students for a job as a Data Scientist, as well as providing a strong background for many other careers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>