<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statistics on Home</title>
    <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/tags/statistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statistics on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:52 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://unodatasciences.github.io/tags/statistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Operations Research</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/operations-research/operations_research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/operations-research/operations_research/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Operations Research is the application of advanced analytical methods to enable better decision making. A plethora of problems may be solved using Operations Research; among these are  determining the route a delivery truck should take in order to make all deliveries while traveling the fewest number of miles determining the best location for a new facility such as a fire station  scheduling airline flights and crew  determining the optimal distribution of bicycles in a bike sharing system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics</title>
      <link>https://unodatasciences.github.io/statistics/statics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 22:33:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unodatasciences.github.io/statistics/statics/</guid>
      <description>Introduction  Statistics is used in a many fields, including biology, sociology, psychology, medicine, economics, quality control, and sports. This diversity, along with the growing need for people with statistical knowledge makes it an attractive choice for mathematics students. Concentrations in Statistics This concentration is recommended for students interested in the theoretical and practical aspects of Statistics, particularly those students who are interested in pursuing graduate study in Statistics or Biostatistics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>